A Finding Aid to the John Henry Bradley Storrs Papers, 1790-2007, bulk 1900-1956, in the Archives of American Art AAA.storjohn
Archives of American Art
- Correspondence, 1857-2007; Series 2; 5.8 Linear feet Boxes 1-7, 25
  - John Storrs Correspondence, 1900-1956; 2.1
    Davis, Garry, 1949
    Dell, Floyd (The Liberator), undated
    Department du Loiret, Republique Francaise, 1944
    Deregnancourt, Alphonse, 1914, 1915, 1918
    Devambez, 1918, 1919
    Deville-Chabrol, Emma, undated
    Diaz, Luis, 1936
    Diaz de Recchia, Ana, 1911, 1913
    Dismorr, Jessica, 1918
    Doubleday Page & Company, 1920
    Dougherty, Paul, 1925
    Dreier, Ethel E., 1923, 1926
    Dreier, Katherine (Societe Anonyme Inc.), 1921, 1922, 1923, 1924, 1926, 1928, undated
    Drury, Holden, 1953
    Dubowsky, Henry, 1945
    Duchamp, Marcel, 1927, undated
    Dudensing Galleries, Inc., 1929
    Duval, Jack H., 1907, 1918, undated
    Duval, L. & L. Janier, 1916
    Eastman, Max (The Liberator), 1918, 1919
    Eckridge, Bob, undated
    Eddy, Arthur J., 1916,undated
    Editions Savoir Vivre, 1919
    Eggimann, L. H., 1918
    Elliott, Lucretia M., 1906
    Embassy of the United States of America, Paris, 1940, 1945, 1946, 1947
    Emmett, Beulah, 1937, undated
    Enterprises Morlon & Fils, 1923
    Espy, John, 1915
    Ewing, Mary H., 1909
    Ewing, Mary James, 1930
    Ewing, W. A., 1916
    Eyskens, A. Mary, 1909
    Eyskens, Felix, 1912
    Fagotat, G., 1922
    Fairmount Park Art Association, 1933, 1948
    Farre, William, 1922, 1923, 1925
    Faucauld, Isabelle de Comtess, undated
    Fauche, E., 1927
    Fenton, P., 1943
    Fio Rito, Madelyn, 1954, 1955
    Fournier, F., 1932
    Franks, Sara, 1909
    Freelander, Ronald, 1945, 1946
    Freneuse, Marie Louise Landry de, 1944, 1945, 1946, 1947, 1948
    Freres, Brunschwig, 1925, 1927, 1928
    Friedlander, Leo, 1936
    Fry, Edith M., 1917, 1918
    Fry, William E., 1909, 1921, 1923, undated
    Fuller, R. Buckminster, 1929, 1930, 1932, undated
    Galerie Briant-Robert, 1924
    Galerie des feuillets d'art, 1919, 1920, undated
    Galerie "L'Effort Moderne" (Leonce Rosenberg), 1919, 1924, 1926, 1928, 1930, 1931
    Galerie Zak, 1925, 1934
    General Alloys Company, 1935
    Geret, Lucien, 1946, 1951
    Germain, Mr. & Mrs., 1925
    Gibson, Sidney, undated
    Golejewski, General, 1945, 1946
    Goodale, Hazel, 1906
    Grafly, Charles & Martha, 1911
    Graphic Institute of Lithography, 1937
    Greeley, Martha, undated
    Green, Gretchen, 1954
    Gros, Gabriel, 1919
    Grossman, Edward, undated
    Gutheim, Frederick, 1946
    H., Edna R., 1921, 1922
    H. W. Croxton & Co., 1933
    Hadley, Louise, 1937, 1940, undated
    Haines, Grace (Mrs. L. Emerson Matter), 1906, 1907, 1908, 1909
    Hammond, Madelyn, 1933
    Hannen, Jos. H., 1909
    Harrington, James (Jimmie), 1900, 1905, 1906, 1907, 1921, 1922, 1937
    Hartley, Marsden, 1926, 1927, 1928, 1930, undated
    Harvey, Fred, 1918
    Heap, Jane, 1923, 1924, 1925, 1927, 1929, undated
    Hecht, Zoltan, 1928
    Heitkamp, Irving & Eleanor M., 1907, 1909, 1911, 1912, 1913, undated
    Helion, Jean, 1937, 1938
    Heyman, Katherine, undated
    Hoeckner, Carl, 1921
    Holabird, John A. (Holabird & Root), 1930
    Holley, Bertha, 1913, undated
    Holmes, Frederick, 1905, undated
    Hoskins, W., 1930
    Houfe, Eric, 1954
    Houston, William, undated
    Hoyt, Henry M. & Anne, 1911, 1912, 1918, 1920, 1921, undated
    Hubert, M. de la Montaigne, 1933, 1935, 1936, undated
    Hubert, Loyou, 1926
    Huddleston, Sisley, 1924, 1927, 1929, 1930, undated
    Hugon, Paul D., 1938
    Hunt, Dorothy, undated
    Iannelli, Alfonso, 1924, 1926, 1927, 1929
    Industrial Fireproofing Corp., 1935
    Jacques Seligmann & Co., Inc., 1934
    Jaines, Louise, 1921
    James, R. Howard, 1911, 1912, 1929, undated
    Jaques, Bertha, 1917, 1918, 1919, 1920, 1921
    Jenkins, Julia, 1905, undated
    John H. Vanderpoel Art Association, 1939
    Joy, Bill, 1922, 1923, undated
    Junior League of Chicago, 1932, 1935
    Kahn, Albert, 1934
    Kayser, Jos., 1947
    Kennedy, Herbert H., 1922, 1923, 1924, 1925
    Kramer, Frank, 1905
    Kunst Art Foundries, 1931
    Lacomme, Risette, 1919, 1920, 1924, 1926, undated
    Lafargue, Henry, 1925, 1926, 1927, 1928, 1931
    Laing, Alice S., 1921
    Lambert, Gertrude, 1911, 1912, 1913, 1914, 1917, 1929, undated
    Laurens, E., 1911
    La Verite, 1919
    Lavolley, I.?, 1926, 1929, undated
    Layrault?, 1923, 1924, 1925
    Lazari, Paul, 1946
    Le Bosse, R., 1938
    Lecomte, Mr., 1928
    Lecomte du Nouy, Mrs., 1948
    Lecornu, G., 1927
    Lee, G. Ambrose, 1905
    Lee, Henry C., 1927
    Lee, Robert M., 1931
    Leger, Fernand, 1936, undated
    Leight, Mrs. Edward, 1921, undated
    Les Muses Francaises, 1920, 1921, 1922
    Lewis, Elizabeth, 1935
    Lewis, Helen, 1946, 1947, undated
    Lipchitz, Jacques & Berthe, undated
    Long, Mason, 1953
    Loring?, Gustave, 1919
    Loyson, 1913
    Luntz, Charles, 1946
    Lyons, Philip, 1929, 1932, undated
    MacBurney, T. N., 1930
    Magnin, A. de, 1918
    Malye, T., 1927
    Mannheimer, Frank, undated
    Manziarly, Yolande de, 1923, 1925, 1926, 1927, 1928, 1929
    Martre, Charles, 1927
    Masclary, Bernard de, 1923, 1924, 1925, 1942, 1955, undated
    Masclary, P. de, 1942
    Marmet, L. J., 1906
    Mazau, F., 1923
    McClelland, Nancy, 1937
    McCormick, Elsie Rockefeller, 1950
    McCormick, Robert H., 1949
    McIntyre, Margaret, 1924, 1926
    McManus, Blanche, 1918
    Medallic Art Company, 1931
    Meeker, Arthur, 1930
    Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1916
    Meunier, Maurice, 1926, 1927
    Miller, Edgar, undated
    Miller, John O'Fallon & Caroline, 1923, 1926, undated
    Miller, Joseph Gilman, 1929
    Milman, Ralph & Helen, 1937, 1938, 1955
    Monnette, Orra Eugene, 1921
    Montellier, J., 1930
    Moody, Harriet, 1925
    Moore, Grace, 1936
    Morgan, Charles, 1933
    Morley, R., 1908, 1918
    Morse, Howard K., 1927
    Morris Book Shop, 1921
    Mowrer, Edgar, 1914, undated
    Mowrer, Paul Scott & Winifred, 1912, 1913, 1914, 1915, 1916, 1917, 1918, 1922, undated
    Museum of Fine Arts, Boston, 1923
    Museum of Modern Art, 1930, 1933, 1934
    "Nadja", 1926
    Nagel, Elizabeth, undated
    Nashville Art Club, 1909
    National Sculpture Society, 1928
    National Soap Sculpture Committee, 1931
    Navez, P., 1914
    Needham, Louis & Brorby, Inc., 1930, 1935, 1936, 1945, 1946, 1948, 1949, undated
    Nelson, Paul, undated
    Neological Foundation, 1940, 1945
    The Neoterics, 1935
    Neue Gallerie, 1925
    Neumann, A., 1940, 1945
    Newark Museum, 1935
    New Masses, 1925
    The New Orient, 1930
    Noel, Georges, 1945
    Norton, John, 1929, undated
    Oakley, Horace, 1921
    Office of War Information, 1945
    Olds, Abbie Storrs, 1950
    O'Toole, James St. L, 1935, 1936, undated
    Paas, Emily Anita, 1928
    Packard, Mary Storrs, 1921
    Palmer, Pauline, undated
    Panama-Pacific International Exposition, 1913, 1916
    Paris-Midi, 1925, undated
    Paris Post, 1946
    Parker, Eleanor Wayne, 1912, 1913
    Parker, Kineton, 1922, 1930
    Partridge, Charlotte Russell, undated
    Pascal, Pietro, 1946
    Pasquier, Gustave, 1924
    Passani, F., 1930
    Pearson, Ralph M., 1928, 1929
    Peignin, Marius, 1925
    Pelzer, Mildred W., 1936
    Pennsylvania Academy of Fine Arts, 1910, 1911, 1933
    Perry, Ruth T., 1907
    Phillips, S. G., (illustrated) 1911, 1914
    Pichon, Leon, 1920
    Pierron, M., 1920
    Playboy, 1919
    Polasek, Albin, 1926
    Ponce, J., 1927
    Post, Mary, 1906, 1907, undated
    Potin, O., 1953
    Provincetown Print Gallery, 1921
    Putnam, Samuel, undated
    Quattrocchi, Edmondo, 1929
    Ray, Man, undated
    Raynal, Maurice, 1928, 1929, undated
    Reboul, Jacques, 1907
    Recchia, Richard H., 1912, 1913, 1920, undated
    Reed, John, 1917
    Rendu, A., undated
    Republique Francaise, Mairie D'Orleans, 1945, 1946, 1947, 1948
    Rerolle, Gervaise, undated
    Richard, E., 1932
    Richard, Paul, 1923, 1927, 1928
    Ritman, Louis, 1909
    Roberts, Webb, 1936, 1938
    Roche, Henri Pierre, 1924, 1927
    Rockwell, 1920
    Roger, Maurice, 1927
    Roosevelt, Theodore, 1916
    Root, Ellen, undated
    Roseman, T., 1922
    Rosenberg, Paul, 1939
    Rotil, J., 1924
    Roullier, Alice, 1920, 1922, 1923, 1924, 1927, 1928, 1931, 1935, 1936, 1937, 1938, 1939, 1940, 1945, 1946, 1947, 1948, 1949, 1950, 1955, undated
    Rowdon, J. T., 1905
    Royer, Jean, 1945
    Ruhlmann & Laurent, 1919, 1920
    Russell, Ann, 1904, 1906
    Safalgette, L., 1919, 1920, undated
    Salmon, Andre, 1921, 1923, undated
    Salon du Franc, 1926
    Salons of America, 1923, 1924
    Saltino, Andy, 1925
    Schoenfeld, Flora, undated
    School of the Museum of Fine Arts, Boston, 1909
    Schulberg, Stuart and Barbara, undated
    Schutze, M., 1934, undated
    Schwartz, Andrew T., 1910
    Scott, Edwin & Josephine, 1907, 1909, 1911, 1912, 1914, undated
    Segur, Adrienne, 1927
    Senior, John L., 1935, 1936, undated
    Seymour, Ruth, 1922
    Shanlow?, Alexandra, 1914
    Sheeler, Charles, 1923
    Shenker, Harry, 1919
    Slaiman, M. & Ruth, 1950
    Smith, C. Powers, 1923
    Smith, Howard E., 1912, 1913, 1914, 1914, 1915, 1916, 1917, 1918, 1920, 1925, 1926, undated
    Societe de Saint-Jean, 1917
    Sowerby, Leo, 1918
    Spaulding, W. B., 1910
    Sprague, Albert A., 1921
    Stearns, Harold E., 1932
    Stein, Gertrude, undated
    Stein, Rita, undated
    Stella, Joseph, 1929
    Stephens, E. A., 1949
    Stephens, Lucille Chandler, 1925
    Sterne, Maurice, 1925
    Sterner, Carl John, undated
    Stieglitz, Alfred, 1930
    Stinson, Roxie R., 1905, 1906, 1907, 1908, undated
    Stora, M. & R., 1926
    Storgo Laboratories (David Goldsmith), 1936, 1937
    Storrs, Frank Herbert, 1924, 1926
    Storrs, John W., 1918
    Storrs, Louis, 1939
    Storrs, Ronald, 1925, 1927, 1928
    Sueur, G., 1926
    Survage, Leopold & Germaine, 1930, 1931, 1932, 1937, 1945, undated
    Tancrede, Robert, 1945
    Tartarin, A., 1930
    The Tavern, 1928
    Taylor, Catherine, 1911, 1912
    Texas Centennial Exposition, 1936
    Thanlow, Ch. L. & Ingrid, 1919, undated
    The Seven Arts Magazine, 1918
    Thomas, Maxime, 1930
    Tillson, Rex, 1923
    Toledo Museum of Art, 1938
    Tooker, Marion F., 1911
    Toulouse, Roger, 1949, 1955, undated
    The Transatlantic Review, 1924
    Truman, Harry S., 1945 (letter to)
    Turnbull, Yale, 1925, 1926
    Tyson, Russell, 1922, 1927
    Vallette, S., 1920
    Valsuani, Claude, 1919, 1922, 1933, 1951, 1955
    Vestal, Donald B., 1931
    Villon, Jacques, undated
    Vinton, Warren Jay & Helen Augur, 1924
    Voccia, Luigi, 1914
    Vogelgesang, Shepard, 1935
    Wacker, Fred, 1955
    Walpone, Marguerite, 1918
    Ware, Mary, undated
    Waring, P. A., 1921
    Warwick, Katherine Murray, 1916
    Webster, H. A., 1920
    White, Charles E., 1932, 1933
    Whitney Museum of American Art, 1933
    Williams, Frederick, 1924
    Williams, Walter R., 1909, 1911, 1912, undated
    Wilson, A. J., 1935
    Wolf, Walter, 1923
    Worcester, Charles H., 1928, 1929, 1945, undated
    Wright, Alan, 1910
    Wright, Katherine, 1921
    Zamoyski, August, 1921
    Zorach, William & Marguerite, 1922, 1924
    The bulk of this series has been scanned. Some printed material has not been scanned.
    Conditions Governing Access note
    This series contains access-restricted medical records.
    - Letters to Marguerite Storrs, 1912-1923 (Box 1, Folder 30-34)
      Partially scanned
    - Letters to Marguerite Storrs, 1924-1955 (Box 1, Folder 35-39)
      see also Box 4, Folder 1-2
    - Undated Letters to Marguerite Storrs, circa 1913-1930 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - General Correspondence, 1900-1905 (Box 1, Folder 41-42)
    - General Correspondence, 1906 (Box 1, Folder 43-49)
    - General Correspondence, 1907-1908 (Box 2, Folder 1-4)
    - General Correspondence, 1909-1910 (Box 2, Folder 5-8)
    - General Correspondence, 1911-1912 (Box 2, Folder 9-13)
    - General Correspondence, 1913-1916 (Box 2, Folder 14-18)
    - General Correspondence, 1917-1920 (Box 2, Folder 19-24)
    - General Correspondence, 1921-1923 (Box 2, Folder 25-30)
    - General Correspondence, 1924-1925 (Box 2, Folder 31-37)
    - General Correspondence, 1926-1927 (Box 2, Folder 38-41)
    - General Correspondence, 1928-1930 (Box 3, Folder 1-6)
    - General Correspondence, 1931-1934 (Box 3, Folder 7-11)
    - General Correspondence, 1935-1937 (Box 3, Folder 12-16)
    - General Correspondence, 1938-1944 (Box 3, Folder 17-21)
    - General Correspondence, 1945-1946 (Box 3, Folder 22-26)
    - General Correspondence, 1947-1950 (Box 3, Folder 27-31)
    - General Correspondence, 1951-1956 (Box 3, Folder 32-33)
    - Undated Correspondence, Alphabetical A-B, circa 1900-1956 (Box 3, Folder 34-36)
    - Undated Correspondence, Alphabetical C-H, circa 1900-1956 (Box 3, Folder 37-39)
    - Undated Correspondence, Alphabetical J-Z, circa 1900-1956 (Box 3, Folder 40-42)
    - Undated Correspondence with Yolande de Manziarly, circa 1923-1929 (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - Undated and Unidentified Letters, circa 1900-1956 (Box 3, Folder 44-45)
  - Marguerite Storrs Correspondence, 1902-1957; 2.2
    Marguerite Storrs' correspondence is with friends, family, colleagues, and others; many of the letters are in French. Included are letters written to her husband John Storrs, many of them written while he was imprisoned in Compiegne, France in 1942. General Correspondence is with friends and family discussing general news, social activities and invitations, her work as a writer, and her husband's career. Many of the correspondents are the same as found in John Storrs' correspondence and include Phyllis Ackerman, George Biddle, Georges Braque, Louise Bryant, William Bullitt, Paul Phillippe Cret, Jessica Dismorr, Katherine Dreier, Madelyn Fio Rito, Marsden Hartley, Fernand Leger, Jacques Lipchitz, Edmondo Quattrocchi, Alice Roullier, Leopold Survage, and Edith Wharton. Many of the early letters are Daville-Chabrol family correspondence, including correspondence between Marguerite and her mother, Emma Daville-Chabrol, numerous postcards, and letters predating the life of Marguerite Storrs. Researchers should note letters addressed to both Marguerite and John Storrs are found among the John Storrs Correspondence in Series 2.1.
    - Letters to John Storrs, 1913-1931, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 1-2)
    - Undated Letters to John Storrs, circa 1913-1942 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - General Correspondence, 1902-1904 (Box 4, Folder 4-8)
    - General Correspondence, 1905-1915 (Box 4, Folder 9-13)
    - General Correspondence, 1916-1917 (Box 4, Folder 14-17)
    - General Correspondence, 1918-1921 (Box 4, Folder 18-22)
    - General Correspondence, 1922-1925 (Box 4, Folder 23-28)
    - General Correspondence, 1926-1928 (Box 4, Folder 29-33)
    - General Correspondence, 1929-1931 (Box 4, Folder 34-37)
    - General Correspondence, 1932-1937 (Box 4, Folder 38-41)
    - General Correspondence, 1938-1957 (Box 5, Folder 1-6)
    - Undated Correspondence, Alphabetical A-Z, circa 1902-1957 (Box 5, Folder 7-12)
    - Undated and Unidentified Letters, circa 1902-1957 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Undated Letters to Marguerite Storrs from Her Mother, circa 1914-1943 (Box 5, Folder 14-15)
    - Daville-Chabrol Family Letters, 1862-1878 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Undated Deville-Chabrol Family Postcards, circa 1902-1913 (Box 5, Folder 17-18)
    - Letters to Donald Booz, circa 1951 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Storrs Family Correspondence, 1857-2007; 2.3
    Found here is correspondence between members of the Storrs family as well as certain family members' correspondence with others. Included is John and Marguerite Storrs extensive correspondence with their daughter Monique (also known as "Monica" and after her marriage, Monique Storrs Booz). Also found is correspondence between John Storrs, his father David William Storrs, mother Hannah, and his sister Mary (also known as "Mae"). The bulk of these letters are from the period between 1900 and 1913 when John and Mary were often living in Europe. These letters range from postcards from their travels to letters with very detailed accounts of their activities.
    Additionally, this subseries contains Monique and Michelle Storrs Booz's correspondence with others, including family and friends, and galleries, museums, and curators concerning exhibitions and sales of John Storrs' artwork. Also found is David and Hannah Storrs' correspondence with others, much of which is with their extended family during the late 1800s.
    - Correspondence between John and Marguerite Storrs and Monique Storrs, 1923-1930 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence between John and Marguerite Storrs and Monique Storrs, 1942-1946; (6 folders) (Box 5, Folder 20-25)
    - Correspondence between John and Marguerite Storrs and Monique Storrs, 1947-1950; (5 folders) (Box 5, Folder 26-30)
    - Correspondence between John and Marguerite Storrs and Monique Storrs, 1951-1959; (5 folders) (Box 5, Folder 31-35)
    - Correspondence between John and Marguerite Storrs and Monique Storrs, undated; (2 folders) (Box 5, Folder 36-37)
    - Monique Storrs Correspondence with Others, 1921, 1929-1980; (5 folders) (Box 5, Folder 38-42)
    - Monique Storrs Correspondence with Others, 1970-1983 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Monique Storrs Correspondence with Bernard and Paule de Masclary, 1961-1968 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Monique Storrs and Michelle Booz Correspondence with Noel Frackman, 1976-2007 (Box 25, Folder 6-7)
    - Michelle Booz Correspondence, 1987-1993 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence between John Storrs and his sister Mary Storrs, 1900-1906; (4 folders) (Box 5, Folder 43-46)
    - Correspondence between John Storrs and his sister Mary Storrs, 1907-1918; (3 folders) (Box 5, Folder 47-49)
    - Correspondence between John Storrs and his sister Mary Storrs, 1921-1930; (2 folders) (Box 6, Folder 1-2)
    - Letters from John Storrs to his Parents, 1896, 1900-1910; (5 folders) (Box 6, Folder 3-7)
    - Letters from John Storrs to his Parents, 1911-1918; (5 folders) (Box 6, Folder 8-12)
    - Letters from Mary Storrs to her Parents, 1903-1913; (5 folders) (Box 6, Folder 13-17)
    - Letters to John and Mary Storrs from their Parents, 1889-1905; (5 folders) (Box 6, Folder 18-22)
    - Letters to John and Mary Storrs from their Parents, 1906; (4 folders) (Box 6, Folder 23-26)
    - Letters to John and Mary Storrs from their Parents, 1907-1909; (5 folders) (Box 6, Folder 27-31)
    - Letters to John and Mary Storrs from their Parents, 1910-1914; (5 folders) (Box 6, Folder 32-36)
    - Letters to John and Mary Storrs from their Parents, 1915-1920; (3 folders) (Box 6, Folder 37-39)
    - Letters to John and Mary Storrs from their Parents, undated (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - Correspondence between David William Storrs and Hannah Storrs, 1874-1913; (6 folders) (Box 6, Folder 41-46)
    - David William Storrs and Hannah Storrs Correspondence with Others, 1857-1964; (3 folders) (Box 6, Folder 47-49)
    - David William Storrs and Hannah Storrs Correspondence with Others, 1865-1894, 1900-1914; (7 folders) (Box 7, Folder 1-7)
    - Correspondence between Various Family Members (Excluding John Storrs), 1847, 1865-1922 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Personal Business Records, 1790; 1855-1987; Series 3; 2.9 Linear feet Boxes 7-9, 25, OV 24, 28
  John Storrs' personal business records consist of address books, records regarding his artwork and commissions, contracts, appraisals, financial records, and other documents regarding professional activities. Artwork Records include scattered exhibition loan forms, records of loans and sales of his work, and various lists of artwork. Also included here are correspondence and loan forms for his retrospective exhibitions at the Corcoran Gallery and Whitney Museum, documentation from art shipping company Lefebvre-Foinet, and extensive documentation of Downtown Gallery's representation of Storrs' work during the 1960s, including correspondence between Edith Halpert and Monique Storrs Booz.
  Commission Files document many of the major public sculptures done by Storrs. Files may include correspondence, news clippings and press material, sketches, photographs, and legal contracts.
  Financial Records consist of correspondence and agreements with financial institutions; bills and receipts; tax, stock, and insurance records; and ledgers recording John Storrs' monthly transactions.
  Also filed here are city adoption documents regarding Storrs' attempts to find American sister-cities for French cities devastated by World War II. Various other documents include records of the Ecole de la Loire artists group (all in French), various contracts and agreements, and estate records for family members of Marguerite Storrs. Additionally there are records relating to Chateau de Chantecaille, an estate purchased by Storrs in the early 1920s as his primary residence and studio, including and appraisals and inventories for furniture, maintenance records, correspondence, drawings and plans for the property, and a guest book signed by visitors to the estate containing notable autographs by Marsden Hartley, George Biddle, and others.
  Automobile records, Deville-Chabrol family estate records, select financial records have not been scanned. Auction posters have not been scanned due to size.
  Items are arranged chronologically within each folder.
  - Address Books, 1900s-1950s; (7 folders) (Box 7, Folder 9-15)
  - Address Books, 1953-1958 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Artwork Records (Box 7)
    - Corcoran Gallery, John Storrs Retrospective Exhibition, 1969-1970 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Corcoran Gallery, John Storrs Retrospective Exhibition, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Downtown Gallery, 1931-1936, 1963-1972; (6 folders) (Box 7, Folder 18-23)
    - Downtown Gallery, 1966-1967 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Museum of Contemporary Art Chicago, 1976-1977 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Norton Gallery and School of Art, 1984-1986 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Whitney Museum of American Art, 1962-1978 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Whitney Museum of American Art, John Storrs Retrospective Exhibition, 1983-1987 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Exhibition Labels, 1935 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Exhibition Loan Forms, 1917-1938, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Index File for Artwork Loans and Sales, circa 1930s (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Lefebvre-Foinet, 1946-1980; (6 folders) (Box 7, Folder 26-31)
    - Lists of Artworks, 1923-1980; (3 folders) (Box 7, Folder 32-34)
    - Notebook, "Etchings and Poems Sent Out", 1916-1923 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Notebook, Record of Sales, 1907-1913 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Notebook, Record of Sales, 1950-1955 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Receipts for Artwork Sold, 1914-1938, 1955 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Automobile Records, 1927-1939, 1944; (Not scanned) (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Business Cards, Calling Cards, Loose Addresses, circa 1900-1940s; (2 folders) (Box 8, Folder 1-2)
  - Business Cards, Calling Cards, Loose Addresses, circa 1900-1968 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - City Adoption Documents, Post-War France, 1944-1949; (3 folders) (Box 8, Folder 3-5)
  - Commission Files (Box 8)
    - Alfred Hammill, 1929 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Brest Memorial, 1928-1937, 1941-1960; (2 folders) (Box 8, Folder 7-8)
    - Brest Memorial, Sketches, circa 1955 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Brest Memorial, Photographs, 1928-1960; (3 folders) (Box 8, Folder 10-12)
    - A Century of Progress Exposition, 1930-1935; (2 folders) (Box 8, Folder 13-14)
    - A Century of Progress Exposition, Photographs, 1933; (Oversized items housed in OV 24) (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Chicago Board of Trade, 1928-1930 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Church of Christ the King, Cork, 1929-1932 (Box 8, Folder 17)